<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">College Management</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="shri_h_h_j_b_polytechnic_chandvad">Shri H. H. J. B. Polytechnic Chandvad</string>
    <string name="applied_science">Applied Science</string>
    <string name="civil_engineering">Civil Engineering</string>
    <string name="computer_technology">Computer Technology</string>
    <string name="e_and_tc_engineering">E and TC Engineering</string>
    <string name="mechanical_engineering">Mechanical Engineering</string>
    <string name="workshop">Workshop</string>
    <string name="department">Departments</string>
    <string name="vision_and_mission">Vision and Mission</string>
    <string name="vision"><b><b>Vision:</b></b>\nTo enhance technical skills of students to meet industry needs along with human values. \n\n<b><b>Mission:</b></b>\nM1- To provide industry-oriented quality technical education to face industrial challenges. \nM2- To inculcate professional skills and human values among students. \nM3- To develop entrepreneurial qualities among students and motivate them towards lifelong learning.\n</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="library">Library</string>
    <string name="announcement">Announcement</string>
    <string name="department_staff">Department Staff</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="course">Course</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="placement">Placement</string>
    <string name="connect_with_us">Connect with us</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="admin_space">Admin space</string>
    <string name="info_applied_science">The motto of science department is to imbibe the spirit of scientific temper and to instill the logical and analytical approach to the budding engineers. It also lays a foundation in the students required for the present engineering and technology core. This department ‘s main objective is to develop in the student, the attitude to imbibe advanced concepts applied in various fields of engineering as well as to apply new concepts to the existing emerging challenges. This department has highly qualified and experienced staff who always focus for the development of the students. They are involved in all departmental activities either curricular or extra curricular. The Academic work of First Year is taken care by Department of Science. It also maintains Parent-Institution communication of First Year. This department deals with the subjects like Basic Sciences, Applied Sciences (Physics, Chemistry), English, Mathematics and Communication skills.</string>
    <string name="info_computer_technology">Our department was started in the year 1994 with an aim to teach computer for students with the intake of 60 students per year in regular shift and now 60 students per year in second shift from 2008.The department of Computer Technology can flaunt of its high profile in the history of the Institution. It has decided and highly qualified faculty members who direct all attention towards teaching and training the budding Computer Technology students and to make them look beyond the obvious.\nOur department has always kept its target by providing computers as per MSBTE norms to the students. We also offer students the opportunity to work on the most sophisticated hardware and software platforms existing in the computer industry. Sharing emerging trends and new developments in the industry, these experts along with the dedicated faculty give students the confidence to take on and successfully execute highly complex and challenging projects.<b>\n\nMany pass out Students are working at various positions in industry, Government, and education sector in India and abroad.</b> \n\n<b>Name of Programme  : </b> Diploma in Computer Technology\n<b>Sanction Intake :  </b> 120 \n<b>Duration : </b> 3 Year\n<b>Course Code :</b> CM</string>
    <string name="info_civil_eng">Civil engineering involves utilization of scientific knowledge for comfort and welfare of human beings. It deals with construction activities of civil engineering structures like buildings, bridges, water supply schemes, tunnels, roads, railways, airports and development of small cities. Utilization and planning of human resource, machines, money and materials.  It also involves waste disposal and transportation. Civil engineering has opportunities in government, public and private sector like PWD, CPWD, corporations, railways L and T, GMR etc. Civil engineers can also become job providers by entrepreneurship and having their own construction industry or registering as a contractor with various government and public sectors. They can also pursue graduation, post graduation and further PhD. The department of civil engineering is established in 1994–95 as the distinction of being oldest department in the institute and producing toppers in MSBTE exam. It has been awarded excellent by EMC appointed by MSBTE. The department has kept updating to well equip laboratories. It also offers training in Autocad and Consultancy in material testing to Government, Private and Public sector. Name of Programme : Diploma in Civil Engineering Sanctioned Intake : Regular  60 Duration : 3 Years Course Code : CE </string>
    <string name="info_mechanical_eng">  </string>
    <string name="info_workshop">  </string>
    <string name="info_">  </string>

    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome Back !</string>
    <string name="login_to_continue_back">Login to Continue Back !</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="create_new_account">Create New Account</string>
    <string name="add_image">Add Image</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="select_user">Select User</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="master_code">Master code</string>
    <string name="add_data">Add Data</string>
    <string name="send_event_notification">Send Event Notification</string>
    <string name="add">Add Data</string>
    <string name="image_url">Image URL</string>
    <string name="add_">ADD</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
</resources>